What a day, what a day, yeah, 80 hour weeks, all work, no sleep, yes
I said you're bound to meet immovable objects, belly of the beast, son, you're bound to get digest
My story never needed a side quest, dancing with the devil, wonder how I ain't died yet
Still in the arena, why they making they side bets, I know they matter, dormy, still the bull get sidestepped
You gotta keep three eyes on the prize, wrong move, turn a king to the lord of the flies, huh
Wise words if you striving to thrive, son, life without knowledge, just death in disguise
I know that life is cold, man, but what's a blizzard to a snowman, sticking to the program
Till I'm in the dirt, I ain't bowing down to no man, it lets you know, be it with flows of the pros, it's all code
This ain't the type of shit to sniff your smoke, but still the type to leave your fiendin' for more
It's the freshest, crushin' with a thousand like flexes, then give it up to God for the pain and the blessings
Yes, yet another day to give my son lessons, another day to hug my wife and ask questions
Another ghost in the shell, just doin' they best guessin'
But let me cook, though I'm chefin', speakin' from the essence, shootin' like Stefan
California dreamin', west side reppin', oppin' hamarama, yeah, these words is my weapons
Flow is so official, you would think I'm reffin', on another level on your head when I'm steppin'
This ain't even hard work, this is life stretchin', these are the sounds of a master mic checkin'
Steady answer the call when faith beckons, and I'll do it all again in a second
Yes
80 hour week